Astounding!
Unprecedented!
Preposterous!
Earth shattering!
Unparalleled!
Indomitable!
Distress!
Agony!
Precarious future!
Ostensible!
Impregnable!
Fatigue!
Dire straits!
Despair!
Public nuisance!
Technicolour!
Hard struggle!
Coming soon!
For crying out loud, that's enough of your idioms already!
Does this not bother you?
Not only has SoLaMi SMILE already reformed,
they've also taken the Dream Theatre
Unveiling Concert from us!
Of course it's buggin' me!
I want the three of us to sing together again.
It's all 'cause Sion screwed everything up.
If you'd just listened to me, we would have won.
Excuse me?!
It's because you jumped ahead on your own!
You're wrong.
It's because you were dragging us down!
R-Relax, you two, relax.
Why don't we think of something
that will help us reform.
Good idea.
However, there's not much we can do without Usagi.
For the time being, why don't we go look for two more members?
Okay!
I'll use my charm and scout us
a crazy awesome team member!
I'll do my best as well!
The fourth prophecy goes into effect now.
Ye best prepare yourselves.
I'm starving!
Here's a special spaghetti alle vongole bun.
It's scrumptious!
Ye best prepare yourselves.
Go! Farewell-usa?!
Capisce!
Pshuu...
Pri!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7...
Brilliant. That's brilliant-kuma.
You're the best-kuma.
You're shining-kuma!
Now that you've reformed, you're shining brighter
and are more cheerful than ever-kuma!
It's tiring, yet still fun!
SoLaMi SMILE has made a complete pri-covery!
Let's do another concert today-pri!
I'm in!
Let's!
Okay!
And while we're at it, let's jump up
the ranks and become Divine Idols!
It's true-usa.
The curse had no effect on Kuma-usa!
Was the curse fake-usa?!
But...
Neko...
Was Neko lying?
There's no way-usa!
But, seeing Kuma like that...
I'm so confused-usa!
You've always been my Go rival up until now, Iroha.
Therefore I think you'd be an exceptionally strong ally.
Form a Dream Team with us.
I humbly...
refuse.
What?!
I am your rival through and through.
I will not team up with you until I defeat you.
Until we meet again.
I see.
You truly are my rival.
I await our next battle!
But of course,
I'll be the winner.
This isn't a laughing matter!
I should continue looking.
Hello there!
Mikan?
Gelrun!
You're always super cool, Sion!
I really want you to join Aromageddon!
You want me on your team?
Sorry, but I refuse.
I'm trying to reform Dressing Pafé.
Dorothy's gonna join us, too.
What?
Dorothy is?!
That's what Aroma said.
Please think it over.
May the heavens bless you.
Bye-bye!
Has Dorothy really?
The two of you are also Major ranked, aren't you?
It'd be great if you two joined our team.
We're roses that can no longer be sold separately-mew.
Our bond is stronger than that of twins-new.
If you'd like to be partners, there are two openings below us-new.
What?!
As if I want to be part of such a lame getup.
Lame-mew?!
It's part of our soul-new!
And here I thought I'd offer my help to those who just happened to be good enough to become...
Major-rank idols after ten years of PriPara.
How rude-new!
We're done here-mew.
And here I was politely inviting them.
Now that it's come to this, I guess it's time to let loose the killer max beam!
Dorothy West.
As I thought, you are a hellion.
It's the demon idol!
Join our team and baptise Pripara in darkness.
What?
What nonsense are you spouting?
Oh!
If you want to partner with us,
then why don't you join Dressing Pafé?
Only Dorothy and Sion are disciples of hell.
I have no use for the timid, plain, and always smiling Reona.
Don't you dare talk bad about Reona, you fake demon!
As if there's anyone who would join your team!
Curses!
She really pisses me off!
However, this makes me want this imp even more!
What a splendidly foul mouth you have.
You truly are my kin.
Sion has already become my servant.
What?!
Sion already joined your team?!
You'd do well to think it over.
Demon Demon Deruderu Beam!
Devidevi Devil!
How dare you, Sion!
Hooray! I got Reona's autograph!
I can't wait to see Dressing Pafé on stage again!
Yeah, if you say so.
All right then, thanks!
Oh, hold on!
We're looking for new teammates...
You got her autograph, isn't that great?
Yeah! I'm really happy!
It's kind of hard to find people.
Reona, have you seen Sion?
Huh?
No.
I haven't seen her...
But what's with that getup?
Is there something you need?
Sion!
I heard about it!
What's this about joining that demon and angel's team?
Huh?!
You traitor!
You're one to talk!
So you've joined their team, huh?
Huh?
Just who are you calling a traitor?!
What?!
You, of course!
No, you!
Calm down, you two!
You're always acting so high and mighty.
You're stubborn and never listen to other people's opinions!
How about you do something about that sharp tongue of yours?
Each and every word of yours is like a thorn!
Go idols are out of fashion!
As is your use of the word "Go"!
As always, you have no appeal!
What?!
This is your end!
You monochrome samurai!
Shut it, you foul-mouthed mushroom!
Stop it!
I'm lost-usa. Hopelessly lost-usa.
Didn't she use these to tell our fortune?
It's true! The curse really is true-usa!
No!
Huh?
Usa?
What?!
She just taped a picture to the back of it?!
Was it really a farce-usa?
It's true-kuma.
We've been had by Neko-kuma.
Usa!
I'll never forgive her for toying
with my pure manly heart-usa!
Exactly-kuma.
Now then, let's thoroughly interrogate her,
and find out why she lied to us-kuma!
Hey you!
How dare you trick us-kuma!
How dare you trick us-usa!
You won't get away with this, you fiend-usa!
Nekon...
Neko, what's wrong-kuma?!
Did something happen-usa?!
Tell us everything-kuma!
We're here for you-usa!
I'm sorry-nekon.
I lied to both of you-nekon.
Neko!
But... why?
I enjoy teasing the person I like-nekon.
I hope you can understand...
a woman's wavering heart-nekon?
When you say "person you like",
do you mean me-kuma?
No, she obviously means me, right-usa?
No, me-kuma!
Me-usa!
Neko.
Anyway, now I know there is no curse.
With this, we can happily reform-usa.
Let's start the ritual-usa!
Hmph!
Usa?
Dressing Pafé is dead.
I refuse to team up with Dorothy.
Teaming up with Sion would be
like teaming up with a pancake.
Huh?
W-What happened-usa?!
It might be impossible for us to get back together now.
Usa?!
What?!
Sion and Dorothy did?!
They said they won't reform.
Even Reona, the one who normally stops them,
doesn't know what to do this time.
I don't have anyone to rely on
other than the three of you-usa.
Usagi's ears are drooping.
I wonder what happened.
Anyway, let's go find out what's going on.
Dorothy betrayed the team?
I never thought she would.
Surely this is a misunderstanding?
That's not all.
I've been tolerating it up until now,
but she always has to get the last word, and I'm tired of it!
This was the final straw.
But...
You're unwelcome here.
This conversation is over.
Why the heck would I apologize?
This isn't some joke!
Sion's the one who messed it all up.
There's no way Sion would betray you.
I'm sure you know that, Dorothy!
Sion's always irritated me to the max.
Always looking down on us.
So do you...
I thought this was just another one of their arguments,
but they won't listen to anything I say.
If you don't find a way to get through to them,
Dressing Pafé really will crumble.
Even if you say that, if I fail...
There's nothing that can get them to reform.
Are you okay with that, Reona?
This is a bit much...
What a sour atmosphere-pri.
Come on girls, don't turn your backs to each other!
Let's talk this out!
Hey, look at me! I'm a snail!
I'm a gorilla!
Ribbit, ribbit! I'm a frog-ribbit!
That's enough. Quit being so stubborn-pri!
Do you really want to stay disbanded forever-pri?!
There's no way around it.
There's no getting over it!
Poor Reona...
It wasn't my intention to be mean to Reona...
I'm sure Reona understands my feelings.
This has to be a misunderstanding!
I'm going to call Reona.
Laala...
1,
2,
3,
4...
Found him!
Reona, are you okay?!
O-Ouch.
Did you sprain your ankle?!
You shouldn't push yourself that hard!
If I put even more effort into it,
I'm sure Sion and Dorothy will...
Reona?
Laala, what is it-kuma?
Reona is going to do a solo concert!
She's going to do it even though she sprained her ankle.
Please come over here, and quick!
Would you like to enter without a manager?
Yes.
Will you be okay with that sprained ankle?
U-Uh... Yes.
Reona!
Are you okay?!
What's the meaning behind this solo concert-usa?!
I promised...
to put on a concert for our fans.
But you're injured!
You need to rest.
I-I won't!
After all, it's my concert!
It's impossible with an injury like that.
You should rest!
I said I'm doing it...
So I'm doing it!
But!
I'm doing it!
Why are you so stubborn all of sudden?!
Listen to others' opinions once in a while!
You're always acting so high and mighty!
You're stubborn and never listen to other people's opinions!
Don't do it, Reona.
Go rest, I'll do it.
No.
All you do is fight, so I can't
leave it to someone like you.
Why would you say something so mean?!
How about you do something about that sharp tongue of yours?
Each and every word of yours is like a thorn!
I get it.
I'd like to help, so do you mind
if we do the concert together?
I also want to help...
We're sorry.
Please let us be a three-person team again.
Hooray!
Don't overdo it!
I was so happy, I forgot I sprained my ankle.
Are you sure you're okay?
Use this to numb it instantly-usa.
With this secret remedy,
I'm sure you'll be able to handle one concert-usa.
Yeah.
Usagi!
I'm so relieved.
I wouldn't want to perform without both of you.
After all, I don't have Sion's stubbornness or confidence,
or Dorothy's unyielding spirit.
But, if the three of us are together,
we can go anywhere!
Let's turn over a new leaf with Dressing Pafé's reformation!
Yeah!
Now that it's been decided,
let's get on with the ritual-usa!
Though, I don't think there's any
helping Sion's stubbornness.
I'm so happy!
They've finally made up-pri.
Promise: Believe in friendship.
Rhythm: Carved in our hearts.
Paradise: Our goal.
We swear to stand on stage as one.
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Coord Change Start!
To commemorate your reformation,
a tight-fitting rock style jacket has been mixed in to form a new coord.
Rock Style Lady Coord!
Go!
The abundant shiny fabric glitters brightly!
Rock Style Lady Coord!
Yay!
It's been boldly designed with a fashionable pattern sporting Dressing Pafé's logo!
Rock Style Lady Coord!
Dressing Pafé!
We've been waiting for this!
Fight!
Do your best-pri!
Go get 'em!
We're singing together again!
This is how it should be!
Let's be a team forever!
Even if I can't do it alone...
As long as we're together...
We can go anywhere!
Making Drama Switch On!
For our dreams! Dressing Pafé Full-Speed Dash!
All Out Full-Speed Dash!
Tension Max Full-Speed Dash!
Fly, balloon!
Relax!
Cyalume Change!
Go!
Purple is cool.
So I got the same as Sophy.
We got blue, so we're pop!
The same as Mirei.
Congratulations on your reformation.
Now go find two more and assemble a Dream Team!
Those fools.
That was cool!
Dressing Pafé has finally reformed.
We'll need to work hard, too!
Yeah.
Though, Aroma and Mikan are really strange.
I wonder what they're normally like?
Your prophecy didn't go as expected.
Both SoLaMi SMILE and Dressing Pafé have reformed.
Time to put the fifth prophecy into effect.
Chapter 6, section 606:
"Starting today, we shall show ourselves to the
human world for the sake of the final judgment."
Huh?
That voice...
Aroma and Mikan?
With that outfit... Does that mean—?!
Gel!
You're students at Paprika Primary Academy?!
Devi...
Aroma and Mikan are
students at Paprika Academy?!
On on top of that, they're also 6th graders?!
The prophesy has reached a new page.
We shall henceforth rule this school.
Amazing!
The angel and demon's broom is...
SoLaMi SMILE, Dressing Pafé,
will you join my kin or not?!
If you join our team, you'll be saved!
First come, first served...
Next time:
The Devil in the Next Class.
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!